Mr Konstantinos Ligas & Son
Emmanuel TV Testimony
My name is Ligas Konstantinos.
I am 56 years old and I am coming from Thessaloniki, Greece.
The young man standing beside me is my son.
People of God: Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
We are here to testify of all the good things God has done in our lives for His glory.
Our testimony goes like this:
I was living in sin and sin had captured me in such a way
that I couldn’t do anything about it.
I went to some churches and also tried to change by myself but nothing happened.
I was living a life of a sin.
I was smoking for 25 years.
I was going to nightclubs, womanising, drinking and doing many other things.
This brought about many problems in my family.
For sure, I was not a good example for my family.
I started fighting every day with my wife and things were not going well at all.
I couldn’t find a solution anywhere.
So, I started praying to God, asking Him to help me because I really wanted to change.
I prayed to God and said, “Lord, I want You to take me to where the fire of Your Holy Spirit is burning
otherwise I am never going to change”.
Then, a friend introduced me to Emmanuel TV.
I started watching Emmanuel TV and praying along with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
What happened in my life was so amazing.
My life started changing through this.
In every prayer, I started receiving deliverance.
What is happening in The SCOAN was happening inside my room
whenever I prayed along with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Mr Konstantinos Ligas & Son
Emmanuel TV Testimony
I mean, I fell down and was vomiting out all the poisonous substances
that satan had put inside of me.
Mr Konstantinos Ligas & Son
Emmanuel TV Testimony
After that, my life started to improve.
I started to experience peace in my life and in my family.
After some time, as I continued watching Emmanuel TV
and praying along with Prophet T.B. Joshua, God saved me twice from death.
Shall we clap for Jesus Christ!
Wow, indeed a wonderful testimony.
For the benefit of our viewers at home - what you are trying to say is that God saved your life,
you were delivered from the addiction of smoking, which lasted 25 years.
Is that correct?
Yes.
And this was affecting your whole family?
Yes, it was affecting me a lot in my family.
I couldn’t find a solution to my problem.
Everything was going wrong.
I was working hard but nothing to show for it.
So, your marriage was at the edge of breaking, right?
Exactly.
All right.
Now, tell us, how did the deliverance take place?
How did you stop smoking?
What happened after watching Emmanuel TV?
As I was praying along with Prophet T.B. Joshua, his prayers had a great influence on my life.
I was praying along with him through my TV screen and everything that was taking place here
was taking place where I was.
Just as it was happening here, I was vomiting and being cleansed.
Mr Konstantinos Ligas & Son
Emmanuel TV Testimony
I was receiving my deliverance from smoking and many other sinful habits.
How many packets a day you smoked?
I was smoking 60 cigarettes a day.
I had become a maniac.
Ever since you watched Emmanuel TV, your life has changed.
Tell us what happened in your family; your relationship with your wife and your children.
There was a big change in me.
My peace was restored.
The desire to smoke left me, completely.
I started to reconcile with my wife and family.
As I was watching Emmanuel TV and God was cleansing me,
some significant things happened in my life.
God saved me twice from death.
I work for the government in the area of sanitation.
I was operating a heavy duty cleaning machine.
That time, a little dog came close to where I was working
and it fell inside the heavy duty machine.
When I was trying to rescue it, I fell headlong inside the machine.
My body passed through many pieces of iron but I came out with just a broken leg.
Here are the marks for the injury.
He tried to save the dog but found himself falling into this heavy duty machine for disposals.
So, what happened then?
How did God save your life?
A human being is not meant to be in such a machine.
What happened?
Mr Konstantinos Ligas & Son
Emmanuel TV Testimony
Immediately I fell inside the machine,
I remembered the words I had heard from Emmanuel TV and Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I received the strength to pray and come out from a small opening to call for help.
Finally, people came to rescue me.
My name is Dimitrios Ligas.
I am coming from Thessaloniki, Greece.
Everything my father said is very true.
God saved my father.
How do you feel, now that your father is free?
I am very happy.
Shall we clap for Jesus Christ!
Mr Konstantinos Ligas & Son
Emmanuel TV Testimony
I came so far from Greece to give my testimony.
I believe that distance is not a barrier.
Everything that happened to me through Emmanuel TV,
everyone who is watching Emmanuel TV and T.B. Joshua can receive as I received.
Congratulations.
We thank God for what He has done in your life.
We would like to encourage you to continue making God's Word the standard for your life,
in order to maintain this wonderful blessing the Lord has given you.
Remain blessed.